Absolutely.  See, I have taken two stocks in Big Stocks for
now.  I'll
try to add a little bit more later.
First came ICICI LBD's numbers.
The numbers are quite strong Ashish.  Ok?   The
problem is that this stock has moved a lot yesterday
and closed at the day's high.  So the positioning has happened.
However, the entire market was closed yesterday.
So what is it?  But profits have increased by 7.5%
and gross premiums have increased by almost 17%.
If there is a gap up, don't chase.
Then you cross weight.  The best way to do this would be to allow
profit booking.
Let the positioning of people finish, which
normally happens between 9:30 and 10.
After that you try if you
get a dip, it is better if you get it below that.
Ok?  But the numbers are good, so
according to that I feel that there is still some movement left
here.  Now the second stock is
delivery.  If you look at the delivery, yesterday
Nexus Funds again sold 1/2% stake for Rs 186
crore.  On April 8, he sold 1.6%
stake.  So now
he has almost sold his share.  Isn't it?  He had 4.5%.
So I am assuming that I have sold half of it.
Now I don't know whether they will sell the remaining half
or not.  But among the buyers, there are
big names.  Morgan Stanley
Goldman Sachs Mutual Fund, these are
big names.  And these are mostly long only
investors.  So according to that, I feel that
selling is getting absorbed.  Like
this whole selling will be absorbed.  I
think the stock will make a big move.  So the
reason why the stock did not move yesterday is
because it was a selling by a big seller.
Because of this, as soon as this selling is absorbed,
I feel that this stock can move big
from here.